The or an area where or.
Or or near and dear War era
where you war out
where. You ignore.
Warrior era
a litter or lawyer the
During a lawyer who is
a litter and. We're
. A little.
More.
To. The East.
The you.
Got. The US.
It has. Happened yet about this.
Now I like that because it's going
to be more of. Thank you to just
get into the Steelers no one brought it up
and if we get caught don't go making up
any stories that I did. On another
level as it is you and your kids.
Want me to go back same.
Just. Looking for me
to rant at every cop and I was tempted to
keep you don't let them find me I always
come runnin them. But
heels to them to stand.
The circus leave town tonight their train
or I think when it does you just follow
me you run with all your might when you
grab on crap tight Don't you worry about me
. You know I.
Know they are. All right to let you
go when your. Heart muscle Let's go.
To new. Don't rub your chum.
All right but take em
home to rent.
Mr No need to see you ma'am share in.
Cyprus to you now.
Good evening Mrs I was that evening. Good
evening Miss diving I have good news Masa
about that Mafia has been fun I know well
it was Walter who was really responsible
for mamma being flown he told the police
or she and that boy Sam Masterson usually
go and that's
a lot of yes father the boy
will be the void where he's
a good boy and he's bright if I
could afford or not send them to
a school like Hi guys I
mentioned it before many times.
Yes madam take the boy to the kitchen and
get him some ice cream and given the
piece of cake to go out on. Average
well. Thank you Mrs Siberians.
You've lost your pupil Mr O'Neill I'm sending
it away I know why you offered to do
to Martha. I know why you made will to do
his daily lessons with us I know you want
him to live here a scholarship a
lot of that's why but I'm not
a foundation Mr O'Neill I don't
care where the water drives
a truck or go to Harvard probably
be a lot happier driving
a truck. You are expected.
Just a minute. Good name Islam and
a tell Mrs I've heard the name of
the take your car as long as I can.
I think of. Now your back ambitious you
know how she feet by that cat I bring it
up to your group. Your
office waiting for you.
Compose
a moment. Though
some.
Look at me. You don't seem very
funny. Ah. Sorry I was.
No matter what you do I will. This is the
fourth time you've tried to run away each
time you were brought back here no matter
how far you go you were brought back you
don't on the whole world enough of them
to make sure that you are always deployed
Bankia you understand.
You understand that.
Doesn't Deserve An attitude Mom Not many
many women would be as patient and this
kind of an on going to girls would be as
on the Great When would you understand
done doing all the see you I'm trying to
walk the distance grime off you make an
eye that out of you again my name is the
same as my father's. Name is ours and I've
had it changed legally I don't
care to don the name as I was
a same as your mother's was before she
was stupid enough to mete out. To
God his power not I want to talk
about my father Bill father with
a nobody in this thing
ever did for us to die.
Was all right Mr. Go up to
your room and get into some
dry clothes after dinner
not want to have you.
Like
a poke at my son. I'm
upset I want someone to.
Lend told me to sneak bundles to you I
thought you'd be hungry so I sneaked the
milk to. She hastily
she ate everything I like
a policeman came to my house this morning
yes me if I had any idea where you could
have gone my father said it was my
duty to tell them fuck I didn't say
a thing no matter what I father told you
ran I didn't say I'll stay. Cold I got to
change my clothes How did the door open
so I can hear you my father says You're
foolish My father says that some day you
will have everything in the world. My
father said that if we only have one little
part of what you will have I can go to
Harvard you know why.
Doesn't anybody the well you scamp do it.
Don't you think I'd better go up
a cheap model right now that will
be all right and if you'll play.
Like. I'm going to change.
My.
Point people to you an outbreak you know
I'm saying things I find myself tell you I
won't say anything funny. Seems all right
toasty ever catch him Sam. I came to take
a bite out of the marsh it's better for
you here I will stake you I hear all you
gotta do is play smart with her I'm going
with you now you listen to me I don't
want to play I gotta go let him go Martha
He's got here will be sent to me from
school Mrs I never said so they got to
catch me first all right Sam if you won't
take me out go without
I'll go off I myself.
OK let's go I want to run
up to Jack I want to get.
A quick. And I'll get.
Any kind. We can account we can.
She said. We were up stairs. He heard
a noise we came down. You saw man
a big man with the. Back
on guard axes its own.
Line.
There's
a line there to pick it up. And
then you won't. Even have. To.
Put down. I think that because we found.
You stairs. For the police.
You'll never get away with it never your
father Police say I don't know I'm not
sure what's going on but Sam what about Sam
He was in the house he saw the phantom
there yes he will be scared that's why I
ran away after that and whatever town Sam
scared he ran away I did nice they've
done all we want and that failed.
I want to talk about. Stuff.
And when the police come. You will
tell them exactly what you told me you
understand. Yes miscount and
you two other yes fuck.
You what you. Will be all
alone in the world. Except
Walter. Wouldn't be afraid
always be with you was.
Never really.
Found last week in
a handicap just like on paper as God is
know what he's talking about chestnut Kings
a dog he will listen racist
a cow ponies years ago in
Tijuana. What do you know
what do you know about that idea like
that sailor. Leave the place when you're
a kid maybe said. One hundred eighteen
years ago when you forget all about it all
of
a sudden you're driving along and smack all
your own hometown up and hit you right
in the face.
And alliance and I come on like
a. Small accident. But after.
The road curve but I didn't come on I've
got to put in divers down for tears.
Next time I pick make I
don't fall asleep. Welcome
diversion. This time I mean if.
We got anybody here to fix this
recognition over and. Then for you don't
like that I believe that I ask you to.
Please.
I want to take up. And tell the little
girl over come back tomorrow open games.
Open that. Up. For my pack
little Johnny ten No four you got that to
come on I'd like for. You shoot you will
strike twice. And avoid
all negatives and I knew.
What it would cost. Although it was done
and I look I want to know now. Take it
someplace else. Welcome diversion.
Program of better music to bring you
a special broadcast in the interest of the
reelection of district attorney Walter
P.
O'Neill. It is with deep regret that we are
forced to announce that Mr O'Neill will
not be able to address the citizens forum
tonight they will suddenly thank him but
we are fortunate to have the best Bob So
I think. The gracious Mrs here in the
studio tonight to speak for.
The issues in this election.
That's enough of that malarkey. Peel in
the listener the kid is live on Sycamore
Street the Saudis to their skills and she
had him you know I'm still. A little
scared to get on Sycamore Street when I was
running for the district attorney I see
ads on what election no
odds no takers this is
a sure bet Mr going to be reelected going
to be governor and I'm making book right
now that some day he'll run for president.
Going to be whatever his wife wants him
to be. And the man right
in this town is to be.
Nice. I haven't. Came into the
whole works after the old lady
died. What do you know
what do you know but.
I know you still look like
a scared little kid. Hey
wait
a minute. Right now you say. I'm the guy
that tossed the rock today I want to watch
you know the guy who chased me by two C.R.
But I caught you. Going to
think that I really did.
You.
Know. You live here is just
who runs this place you
need
a name and this is but she's not home it
waiting for just came back to get my things
. In a way to go out and wait for
a taxi I still am in this house
seventeen eighteen years ago was
born here kidney yielded in that. I
didn't move right after I was born
calendar stay I got to match and he's.
Got the time at quarter after eleven
that just dandy that got eleven
thirty bus to catch still might have to
text doesn't show up fast knowing that he
lives are on air name of mass. No
know anybody in town at all then.
Is your name asked. You mean you're
just getting home after eighteen
years. Seventeen it just getting
around looking up you people are not
exactly. A step to be driving through
on the way west. More or less curious.
What you going to do. But I mean I
mean about you people I don't know
I mean I think maybe tomorrow
I'll get out of the courthouse in
a couple of deaths in the last eighteen
years can you do that yeah I think so.
And I.
Bus time no please hurry I've
got eleven thirty bus to catch.
The connection to see you again
I gave you my last much list in
a place on the way to the bus
station talked me into it.
Got my matches got
a name. Tony and Tony. And
Tony American. Is that
a delay Mr Masters.
Please hurry the depot is just across
the tracks he still got four minutes.
Made a dip you didn't stop to pick up
your chips Mark you are chasing I can get
a bus back to the kill tomorrow. Maybe I
won't get about three. I'll go some place
. It in another direction.
Or for the whisky.
Have you ever been out
west. Maybe I would.
Like.
Do you want to go back can compare
has got some pleasure. Do you
drink him. Drink by you.
Too bad you only check your bag with
stationery I don't know I guess I wanted
a hotel you want me to take
you there you have to be it's
a good hotel. Now can I go there. It's
a public place. So it's like it's
a Masterson wants a room for
a young lady should register when
she gets there yes thanks keep it.
Classy. Blue lights music
everything I can say.
I lived in this town they were nothing
but saloons my father used to live in
a. Month you. Were related. I
don't think you had to do much
scotch. Take
a plain water chaser with that Scotch
is it good to out of jail. If you
drive for. Six hundred miles and
it's morning. Like driving anything
tonight my Stanley Steamers in the garage
have interface that. Better bring us
a couple more for
a soft. Two dollars. On Me Thank you.
I'd like
a drink just fine you keep. My mother
wouldn't approve of that. Original after all
this time after all this time you probably
wouldn't care one way or the other. Toko
focal Glenda got them don't let slide is
a big family our personal side we're
just the usual two people necessary to
increase the population.
My left when I was
a baby and my father. Probably drank himself
to death but now the man I know talks
cold like that my dad. Is the most
cold blooded man in great detail.
To kick me. Can guess where you didn't
break your neck to catch that bus back to
original. When it got on and got
off the porch started. They got to
finish minute I got on. The way
it's gone now for tonight any.
Hope you know the one to tomorrow night.
Now I know for sure I'm not gonna make
that neither. Wonder returning.
But I'm so glad you came to have
a drink with me tonight I was so lonesome
much like two died. Because you haven't
been that long I want to live that as
much as you can hold without Ashton open
I don't know my dad that leaves.
Her for you. She would go home.
At least not take the hotel your
hotel is really pay you rent
a hotel advertising on that. You're smart.
And he think I've been trying too hard
to get acquainted. Maybe it has to do you
think that's wrong maybe it's too soon to
tell. I wonder what you're thinking I don't
think you'll take it too much room in
my Stanley Steamer if you're already.
Thinking the hole that far away to the coast
.
The of. The way here for better. There are
some. Parallels like a scared
little boy you listen just in
a crying that's what the wife.
Mr kneeling on the top of my knowledge.
Was.
No words. And singing.
My lady's really caring for some coffee
for you no thank you I have another drink
water. If there is to
be a discussion I need
a hearing other while actually there in
here and we go here when and if I reply to
an every day you say you forget that you
are supposed to speak to me. I didn't get
a. Nice. Room I mean. A
long time since I've been here where were
you kidding around where I was still
a people's choice I did not make
a public display of myself in any way you
realize of course that you will one day
inevitably inevitably. Go Korean or.
What's my and your as you think
I'm entitled to an explanation. But do you
want me to say I don't want to put words
in your mouth I prefer that you were right
when did you get drunk Where did you get
drunk why did you get drunk.
Don't stand over me like that.
Am
a sentimental man my wife and I started
to get dressed. Then I realized it
was the fourth anniversary of my father's
there. A lot to be nice about I went to
the cemetery and laid
a wreath of flowers on it grave however
I never got their sentiment over
here. I stopped off to have
a drink do we sainted memory as I
drank I thought to myself it's such
a pity that my father isn't alive to be
able to see for himself or his dreams come
true dreams he works so hard. His son
a famous man. Married
to a beautiful and well
a woman. Right now tell me why your
current because I couldn't get up and
speak before people. Will to listen to
me what's done is done the deeds
done not the thought it got
a life to live I don't know much brilliant
career my father always said Father was
right he was never right about anything and
the day he walked in and found you out
on the floor I told you I never want that
mansion the de sac side you in the court
room side the Public Prosecutor demanded
that the state take the life of
a man for the brutal murder of Mrs Iverson
my father said nothing and I looked at
him but he said nothing your father was
a really stick man my father may he
rest in peace was agreed. That any
executed was
a criminal if he hadn't Hank that he would
have hanged for something else man was
a man and justice is justice and. That's
the way it is I. Can't get up and speak
before. The words stick in my
throat. I rather get drunk.
I do get drunk. It can.
Go to listen to me if you carry
a thing in your mind it makes you sick I
want you all that to morrow will be like
today you will leave on a
trip to your health for
a few weeks will you but
would you now stay here.
And I'll stay here. What do you want to
do give everything up that would you want
to do you wouldn't let me do that would
you much do you want to. Know why I ask
myself that question all the time if
my father were alive I could ask him.
Only I know what his answer would be
each day to me keep what you have.
Make
a lever to. Make an impact or bark and
that's what I am living up to and want to.
Drink left.
By them.
Or or. Tell me my what should
I do about my life you.
Can remodel high don't abandon all that.
I don't just throw it back in your face
you tell me. If you.
Know this is not good not bad what
I have. With Baffin come out come
out wherever you are with bad. There's half
as many bands as there is room to have
the rooms has beds and has it that's one
way of looking at it another is for each
two rooms one has
a bath in the middle and the other
hasn't or you might say there's a half
a bed to each of two rooms I was
again on this have as many bears as
a race runs I never heard of them to parrot
I've already sent the boy with those
bags up to your room Mr Masterson or will
they belong to us merchant you they came
in my name because she
wasn't registered I just met
a stranger oh it's too bad. The
boy went off at twelve you'll have to
manage yourselves I can't leave the board
likes. A night. Sweet Dreams good night
Cuban. Twenty five euro number twenty
five I'm twenty three next neighbors when
you.
Why did you buy
a ticket to Ridgeville if you didn't want
to go back. I didn't I didn't buy the
ticket I got it but I can buy.
Your eyes. A little cold maybe
better get out of this would.
Have started too bad for
you now i'm next thanks.
To move.
Move. OK.
Alone you both pick up
a cigarette. You don't mind
the kind of parties. At
times that they should tingle something
very personal about so it's almost as
personal as a toothbrush I will use you to
fresh Where's your book. Killer kind of
a book The suspense is killing is not
somebody you're before forgot. Left.
Alone just.
As one in every room of the hotel. Want to
practically every room of every hotel in
the world. Tells all about
it then first pages.
Of what do you know. And
I don't I don't care.
To look at you. It's really
a picture. From you Maggie. So
you're leaving tomorrow. For eleven to
discourage fixed sure you don't mind me
being a pest you know. That
a co-pay. Are you going to stay
in the West maybe maybe not.
You might get lonesome again you know some
before I was so lonesome that I like to
die and I know you mentioned
that. I tried to tell you why.
I'm going to take
a shower I just got out of jail.
Just got out tonight. Like
I said. We leave tomorrow.
Thank you like.
The and.
When actually. They.
Are.
I don't.
Morning Mr Massey. You know
that show me the. Smile I know
is that they want to save.
The chicest that's it ask you
a couple questions. To Spencer
skill and what they want to know
you've been around. Look at that Africa
and see all the Normandy on it you add
it back in your coat same reason you don't
wear your bad tell I couldn't cut what
else do you want to know what we wanted
to know this layout told us right nothing
you can add to it.
She didn't get an accident and
she stayed in the can for
a nice long scratch but to charge violation
of probation probation for was that ten
to probation when she was released
yesterday it was a two week into
a home in Richmond an hour ago we picked
her up at the depot and she tried to cash
the ticket maybe she wanted to go by train.
I mean you want to walk there's no law
that says the reason she gave no the
reason she gave was that she got
a job she said you were employed what's
wrong with that and if you can prove it
take
a tip from me but don't try it Jake and they
don't like to waste that time testifying
in court but we will. So on.
Exhibit A but if you get
stuck you know wait
a minute cops are. Right labor things
alone you want to come along shoulder.
A little scared boy. You're
just about to do your old pal
a great big place. I
don't like the way the election's going
this beautiful morning the election's going
to go to every morning. On
a. List Thank you. Bobbie.
I can I do for you and in but not
yet ready to face the world. I
want to sit down. On the I'm
in kind of a hurry to take
a note and call me funny but it.
They called in
a. Little
bit. Of a gentleman to see you have
a very important. Little I don't want to.
Have
a minute time in my house. To. Lose
. A family mad. On her own we
were kids together Miss and
you and I would notice and I went and
I mean really water only I said I
a fact checked all this of course I don't
want to be disturbed unless it's very
important yes Mr O'Neill.
Along with then home Sunday night eighteen
years something like that. We just can't
remember the three of us.
Three A. Thanks but you like
water. I'm married and I know
you've done all right I guess.
And what have you done
knocked around and seen
a lot I guess you know had some fun maybe
already done most lately I mostly most
gamble I mean gamble sure sure that's my
business perhaps this is where I should be
my act of life is
a gamble and it about and out somewhere
and you needn't have made that point.
Size and stuffy conversation
I told you like a drink
a little early in the morning I haven't
even stopped for breakfast check the
occasion. He talked me into it fine.
Nice of you to look me up so that
I wouldn't about your
water all night. I met
a girl on you can help you don't look like
you need help with any girl this trip
out I do kids in jail What's
a chat violation of probation name is Tony
merit check that's not easy to squish
Now you can do it you will
for old times sake or old
times sake. Using.
This only all hearsay you please have
a way. She usually drops in on our
way down to what like to see here.
And this is only
a comment yes. One
sorry I didn't know you were that they are
right hello hello my name is Master Sam
asked on south.
Sami now. Oh. Oh oh. Oh well I'll do
that again L.O.L.
. You should have called me just
came in. Well you are going
to be
a big boy to him I always was big for my
age member. Yes SAGAL on anything else you
remember. Well there are lots of
things I never figured that get
a little much would grow up so beautiful.
I thank you for my wife sounds
funny but over the years
saying my wife died.
Oh I don't get so what I mean well I've
always thought of Mark is you know how if
you keep something in your
mind since the time you're
a kid how long you think for him at
all depends on district attorney. I
may have to put on
a couple of hours and have
to paint so it's hard. I
don't want to be disturbed
Well that's why Walter you're
a busy man so I will and thanks
thanks for everything. So.
Much you glad now you missed that circus
train. I don't know where I reach you all
the hotel and you will do that for me
want to order I try my best you did it
and here's hoping you win that
election OK I will watch your thank.
Sure sure thing but I get it sure
thing is never again you know what
I tell you give it that affect. It.
Easy characters and thank you. Very sure
of himself you know it well as this is the
first time I've ever seen
you off balance. I was glad
I was. Can assure. Me to.
Sam will never tell I'll never forget you
saying that what makes you think he will
what makes you think he won't.
I won't even hear you came in
last night to tell you what you found South
where he's been what he's been doing I
thought you'd ask what he wanted. But
then when he's playing it's mine.
There was always this one all he wanted
was for me to get his girl out of jail.
Because that's what he said he was. But
you took even before they can get He's
a gambler
a sharpshooter running boy they come to my
office by the hundreds Couldn't you see
black man in his eyes. Having
heard the can you wear them it
starts to shake you down and he's to go
maybe he'll just take up and leave leave
you think you leave
a touch with million there's only one
way you'll find an. Release the good.
Design is in town. You know me
and I want a routine check out of Samuel
Madison nonresident register gave
a hotel to St John close the door I want
to routing check of all garages one of
them had his car stay here
I want to check up on
a local bank get that right detective
work on the number come back.
I might improve my mind while I waited.
Cosmo's life John Surely you didn't expect
to wait that long I was just going to
look at the pictures I found your message
when I got back to the hotel I asked you
to phone and figured you wouldn't mind if
I came in person I figured you would
why you impressed me this morning as
a man who would bet on anything almost
anything depending on the odds that you'd
like me the story of my life for you but
my story against you is. You've got that
let's say you that you left here September
twenty seventh one hundred twenty eight
will start from that exact date how come
that's as clear in your mind I shouldna T.
And I used to think this was one spot in
the world but you really made it just that
is to be so Doc another
thing when she I hate it.
Come on now show you what I've done
with the rest OK fine I'm going on
a rubberneck tour in years soon after my
aunt died there decadence of this type
wanted to try was the House and Senate
is cool but Mr O'Neill Mr you've got
a formal about your husband I
actually know I was speaking about
a spot they tell me it was my tutor you
were in that hall after my aunt died he had
little to live here. I was
cozy. This is was his room.
Rich. RICH Well you you live here all the
time and except for the few years I went
to college Mr on the outside Well the
thought that was father thought it would
be good for me to get away for awhile Mr
O'Neill waters father he sort of took care
of everything and I guess as he took it
in like that let's talk about something
else I want to talk to the subject. This is
the dining room. And
a kind of crowd. All right. I pick
waters myself and I wanted to marry him
when I know why I ask when when I finish
school all right now why did you marry him
. I can have
a subject at your time you. An
open book I want out of this
town with the circus go on you are supposed
to go and make friends with the animals
and live happily ever after almost
almost. I got ambitious and that
toward the good. Guys I wasn't satisfied
just being friendly with the animals I got
so I wanted to own and so I bought some
animals well my lion got the mange and gave
it to the monkeys the animals
became a responsibility and
a liability I lost all my hard earned cash
and ran like a thief out of there with
a great end to become friendly with
people. And I had some success maybe in
a gambler and people being what they are
well I bring this up to my twenty first
year when I became
a man officially How did it feel to become
and then officially I feel I've done
that before how did you
feel about becoming
a woman officially. I
thought had been there too.
This is the room that you used.
During the San. Do I It's
the only room I didn't change. It seems
that only yesterday I came through that one
we were going to run away together
that night. You do know and.
It was warm but man. I
come here often the same.
Little girls grow up. They never get
through playing with dolls it was
a storm that night come tonight. I was
afraid of the sun break that night she told
me or. I didn't want you to know I wanted
to be like you never said anything.
You remember that too don't you say. Things
come back to you don't say it like that
to make me feel good that because it's
cruel All right it's true we were just
a couple of kids. We're not kids now
you know Moffet we're not kids.
No time for greens. Only one dreams and
it came true you are here so is water
about wasn't my son Tom I want you to
understand I understand. I understood when I
saw both of you together in the office I
watched the way looked at you never saw
Guy so not about anybody in my life than
if you stay in August or I'm not staying
in I was. All right Sam what do you want.
Oh I want yes why did you come back you.
Rode her but I didn't ask her name.
And now wait
a minute. You sound like I have to. A
matter of fact you sounded just like your
aunt used to. Have made me don't have
a baby I will be around long enough to
remain in the certain young ladies out of
your husband's clanked and I carve out
a Dempsey's alleged garage. I'm headed west
I think you really mean any objections
. It is not
a fight and should have known
what. You. To be like.
And. Sided you ever next.
Year for old. Or are.
Poor.
Actually garage Oh yes Mrs
O'Neil this was cruel Neil. Yes
man. It was
a rush job anyway and I'm Russian up as
it is don't mention it I have to be of
service Ms O'Neill. If I
add this to your report.
This O'Neill don't like this guy
to go not yet I didn't say thanks.
Thanks thanks. There's not much to report
on him locally out of town reports are
still coming in you'll have
a complete file on him in
a couple of hours he looked like so far
the big shot gambler broke many times but
always turns up with
a new bankroll the police in every state
are trying to find the source of this
money but no dice and they are at no
convictions beat or murder appen fresco self
defense has
a war record few can equal the condoms his
grasp of the ownership certificate says
he owns it what's wrong with it smashed
ready along to take effect well.
Who didn't he get this call from him to
check that yes I checked it and who was it
Mrs O'Neil.
Yes Mr O'Neill in the county jail I
want to protect the women's division.
I have a county jail for you Mr
O'Neill deputy elect Baker. L.
Girl I want to call you about
before. I bring her out here
a date I want to talk to.
You got time bud. Banks my friend on
a few minutes. Say I can see your
face around here before. I'm
a stranger. And you went
by the money. She's
a stranger to she's due out
a couple of hours and. A
lot of travelers and I checked the laws
very specific on violation of probation
it's the civic about if we. It's serving
a five year sentence so I was told once
before you lied when you were picked up you
told the police you were employed by Sam
Mathis if think they would believe me Todd
told you to look up that story between he
had nothing to do with it very fond of
him and you wouldn't want anything to happen
to him that he feel the same about you
you would want to serve out that five
year sentence which is what do you get
Remember five years and this time
you have to serve every day.
You don't have to. Get down
to what do I have to do.
Tony. Tony.
O'Neill foamy told me the architect. Sure
the district attorney is no friend of
mine I skimmed it do me
a favor and here you are years late but
free except the last paper I got worried
about. American. Comic. Got me.
I'd like a drink. Here I sent ya by a
dozen a taxi I'm going to toss you
a real coming out party exactly. The.
Right. The guy.
I'm it's wonderful I think
you'll like it. Go ahead eat.
Just time not. To mention another. Kind of
data type Spanish jam forget it now you're
out it up with the name you know what I
mean or to me. A couple of times last
night I tried to tell you want to time
it would listen I don't want to now oh no
you've got to plead my make you feel any
better I want to be sure you understand.
One to five thinking. One to five years
it is so long ago it's bragged. That
three months before I came to town.
And happen to the best of people I'm not
the best in people I'm just Tony married
King. Or you get for Cotto
need to judge me. Met
a guy I told him he said he was in
love with me he gave me the coat
a likely story. I simply did
true every word of it at
a tried to point to because I needed the
money. But as the many I don't know I city
he took
a pottery he blew We flew to the moon.
You don't fly Tony the judge says the
judges that can do one to five. Hours
how come I gave you probation.
First. You know like
predation is. If you're
a knife sticking in your back. Still
looking out for the cops relax now you're
free I don't contend that. Can only take
you back to hotel no no no
please. But if you want.
To. Get your coat on the to
get back get your coat I
killed a gag. I was up to you have
a nice layout you get double rooms
connecting DUIs and tall quests but this guy
tell you give you twenty picture I don't
need any trouble to get She's my wife.
Or you can have
a. Spate. Beat it you two.
Just want to make she'll go there don't
have to be no trouble there don't have to
be enough there's got to be certain ways
gays have to be total less certain ways
gay said Why do you want to tear out. It'll
do me. As an alley to the kitchen door
. And.
Stay here.
In this well.
In fact.
It is the ears.
What happened to you. I think
it's made up for our way.
A little. Earlier.
Tonight.
But you catch them actually.
Trying to continue to. Read it I
think maybe I got it committed or
why. Risk I keep trying to come on get
down before they let me out because we did
a decent piece for new is named waterhead
actress that's me all right they took it
a ways off Judge me
a lot of questions mostly about you not
me about you and she kept us to be funny
why you can hear yes me
that could but I was
a lot of Christians I forget I remember I
had mixed up with the goods the the ones
who worked with you they just wanted to
scare you need as much intel they could if
I didn't pay we cannot go back
to you today no no the as
a minister and he was there by day two
they said they wouldn't hurt you much no
more proof they said if I went for
a good hope but they said if I
did. I would marry. Him I've
got it.
On a single common kids
a break. Back that they don't want to hear
Sam I don't know what you got I don't
want to like it or not they don't know how
to be loved. I don't like to get pushed
around I don't like people I like to be
pushed around I don't like anybody to get
pushed around. But
what do. You. If you have the
next bus stop I'll meet you
wherever you say I'll go back with you.
I wanted to say the.
Moment. Thank you Mr O'Neill and you
will get hurt as Mr Masterson hardly
recognized. Your Man Ask Mom.
Tell Mrs O'Neil that you know.
About we ought to have
a little talk. To kick off first
your team or mine and apparel and.
Evan.
Report on Sam Masterson.
Take this on to up on you.
Out of shape water for
a minute that you would that. I
would. I wasn't going to show you
I wasn't going away say come on.
If again that this was your
out. I could've given you
a much more detailed picture on Sam
Masterson I don't know you can add. You
know it now. Now let Martha give
it to you given what's in the
facts concerning
a guy called Sam Masterson and its attitudes
towards life and love war it's got the
wrong ideas to me I. See the other
guy what happened this fell
out of
a guy's pocket and hit me in the face
hypertext what the trouble was we're going to
trust your own cops.
Your rights and I hired
a man to work to over the idea was mine I
thought it might scare you when you're
not coming back it has We're ready to
listen to the kind quotation on blackmail.
Blackmail I said blackmail now what is the
price remember you're dealing with two
old friends. Which one of you do I
deal with let me be at my office at
the plant a tree OK. And I had
a deal be profit on it whatever the
price is that it don't try this again
what happened last night can happen
again and worse don't try it we've had
to make this
a flat statement. Kill you. Want
to have an abortion.
Trying.
If we're. Using pain if you're. Not.
Very lucky and the stupid in the afternoon
he told me he didn't want anything that
he was going away let me have didn't
like what you had in mind. It's quite
a thing in a small city like this to be
a difficult time. To get to be like
God. You know everything down to the
smallest detail. Even
a call to tempt him to run.
Sam's leaving Iverson today.
That's what he said I want to hear you say
to him No it's up to you I know you you
are my life's work I've studied
you all this here. Little girl in
a cage waiting for someone to better out.
And along comes. You know what's on my
mind about family. And I think I'm.
Going to tell you this. What
you don't have to think I'm
a trouble no no I had him take
it out right he's still just
a scared little kid coffee
please but I'm not as
a one I can't help out but his own ale the
three of us grew up together I told you
about and I'm. What's she
like now I mean. She pretty. Beautiful.
That's why I can't figure out why should
a beautiful rich girl stay married to
a guy she's not. You know that I know.
You sound like you're in love with you.
Sound like you're jealous. Could be.
When we even see things carting.
What do we do until then. I know why
don't we find out what happened
here people. Really simple I know
I left come September twenty seventh and
twenty eight exact day how come you
remember. When you remember
a date the exact date about that night on
the not less than thing trying to get.
Going to finish your coffee with the down
of the newspaper most of the month. I
think I can find out my people
down there afterwards take
a shot. Or
strange case one on a saw for
years. Then one day they picked up
a guy who stuck up a garage
so someone used to work with
a lady Iris House came out
of the trial and it was
a want to knock the old lady off it's my
favorite case Picture of the guy. Doesn't
look like very much to carve
a scared little rabbit I watched him
all through the trial never had
a chance O'Neill really did
a job on him that Walter O'Neill they
have same guy kind of dramatic though him
being engaged needs the murdered
woman. To do the job. Jury was not
missed what happened was I saw
him interesting a solving
a murder after all those years so all
the files ago had read enough times on.
Yes that's been matched by
a point sentiments A. Thread clock on the
nose on the now scum and Sam should have
kept me waiting big exactly as always keep
people waiting did you know that good
executives don't have that you're good and.
It catches it doesn't that the feeling in
the factory when you're out on this place
I couldn't get past the gate now I'm
a guest or am I and I think you
oughta did your Apple T.V.
Everything I was her only Yeah. That's
a Get the way she left that night standing
in the doorway leaning on her cane I
don't talk about OK OK it was
different then you did this one
clean and fresh Well it's
a perfume I use it makes me smells nice I
bet I smell as nice as you and water put
together. What do you want I think
I've got what I want I think I've got
a gimmick again because an angle it works
for you to keep you from working too hard
for yourself so specifically
what is your I specifically
asked half of what you tell me.
Come here. My father used
to work at the mill hand
so did my father when I was so
no I own or even now I'm easy.
I was twenty one when I took it over it
had three thousand workers and got thirty
thousand. Renaissance that gate now go down
to the edge of the river. And I did it
all by myself. Without Walter
without his father. Or by might.
After this should make quite
a score. Half would make
you my partner. That's
what I had in mind you went out of here
a dirty little kid once before that can
happen again I don't have to give you
anything if I don't want
to but you do want.
Ain't going. Nowhere.
I go wish I went shopping anyway I should
make it you got it if you good yeah I'm
high I had a drink well if you need
a bucket ago the dice came up seven Tony
you bring me luck I'm gonna wear you like
a charm. You really think so when you
really think I'm pretty lucky I was so and
that's an asset for a guy in my business
County and I can catch twenty a marriage
a good kid do stick around to any marriage
act and I've got. Plenty that way
every time mind you on the
street no girl asked you for
a cigarette and alleged in the time.
Like this panic at philosophy good
to. One in
a hundred meters. To
be. Even if it's over.
Look what you don't know don't talk about.
The button you have I'm
sure you well let's take
a look at it. Ninety five how
do you like it. With you and it
is. There. Going.
I heard you talking or even
a crummy hotel like it's
a switchboard I had to show privileges
in this hotel the same. I own.
It on their time. So this is
a good. Tone is my name and
Tony and Meg. Done To this day
while at the same ship that just that you
forgot to develop. Again I give another
showed
a club in your room or here. Tony Yes.
There's only
a sorry she said in the past
said. OK forget it. Tony. I'm
going out with this on the island this
is. Why you came here and is. Only back
a little. I got no place to go see you.
I didn't like them that apologized it was
nice on your town if you want me to say
anything else to spoke your face. To
get out of here I've never been in
a hotel bill like than different I've been
in too many just the way you read about
it in books Windowshade
a scotch on the crest. Next
day yes now one that we can
order I get here I don't
like room service.
Old much atoning magic really.
That's what she asked me about you.
Buddy
a friend for. She's very independent
high place. How did you meet. Lived
in the same house and I just.
Went now. Now and then.
Let's go back for
a. Number the continue with your
anti-American few others in town
actually cares. And by those.
And we don't like some of the same
people and places. Sounds like
a very substantial beginning. How
long have you known of in. This day
before yesterday. How long have you known
me. But I'm not sure that I've ever known
you. The same going on the best.
Way to. Yesterday check. With you
so.
Went outside and wanted to play that's.
Going to fulfill your focus with. That
guy when he sobers up tell him I run an
honest book I always pale.
But I told you to wait outside I wanted
to sing so he wanted to count didn't you.
And.
Assist but. Like
a car. You know what happened the last
wife until I'm back. To be turned
into a pillar so old what
happened a lot you got
a way to look back you know your Bible you
would too if you spent as much time as I
did in hotel rooms I'll take it up. Come
on let's get out of here island what. City
from this past. Year doesn't even
material it's real area
owning it gives you
a sense of. It now what I meant
if. I was there was that.
If anyone asked in my name now I
tailors my ass with. Smelling smoke.
When some can't bear. Bandung. We used to
come up here when we were kids and girls
. It brings.
Now is days we used to think
that this was free. And then. At
me even exist. Just now you looked.
Funny you hadn't run away.
I member waited
a long time in the rain which you didn't
show. In this address. On here had left
town. New and attend. But it's just.
An Afghan now it's too late. Much
to do. One thing led to another.
Another one. I want to
talk about and. I had.
None of them. Would have been
so different if you had.
Been you instead of wood.
Or. If you would stab me.
When I left the cane Why didn't you stuck
it on your own how much I hated you why
didn't you stop me I was in and
then I stood there and doing.
It was there no. I wasn't there I left
when your aunt came into the hallway
I didn't want to stick around I was in
a scrub was it was I never so I had I never
knew until tonight about your add to it
the one I hold my hand and
the little water killed.
A thunder and.
An end and. A
man. I am
an. Them help me help me
right now. Tell me talk.
And ever imagined anyone could die so
quickly. I'd always supposed to wherever I
went she would be with me that she
would never die. But it wasn't like.
I expected to find her when I went back
in my room. Later I became frightened.
Because the place was
sympathetic they kept
a very attentive. At least my stories
and when I told the world from.
That mess that had. Peacefully How
did you sleep I'd have to become
a man. Alone I found out why would his
father believe my story. Was this is my
manhood never died he took a place.
He wanted to make something of
a son that was kind to them both to him
that. Became so unbearable that I wanted to
tell the truth. But he delivered they given
me said to them to begin again to take
a picture of what would happen to me that
I was crazy with fear. Is that the able.
To increase that he
made me kind of the not
a crime. My testimony I sent an
innocent man to the gallows.
He used it to make him in
a world. Champion not going to go
away again and I want you here
Sam I believe so much inside of myself
to kill to the want to be something else
that we didn't breathe.
Air in room to. Namely.
That
a load of. My
month. Old Ayla you.
Said. A little an.
Age.
When you.
Well I just got up. And I.
Made Sam and.
Man of adventure light and. While I
was sound asleep I got heavy. OK.
I've got something to tell you time. And.
Tell me.
You're crying because you said.
You were the one that there was
a girl that. Well that's
what I came in to tell you.
It didn't have to stay. In the
streets at least. I wanted.
To see that. It started
a long way back I I don't know yet
how it's going and what they did.
What he what they did do I don't know. Could
be the truth. Like you did when I was
going to work to be you. Know or even.
Be. Sorry.
But. I'm sort myself that you.
Believe. You want to leave. That's
a cute. I mean I. Don't put
it that way you're here
because that's the way we wanted.
To. And it's not to.
I'll be able to out I want to speak to Sam
I asked for that phone Hello Sam This is
Walter I know I'm not
disturbing you bought a desk
a man. Already I want I want
you to come up here now
right now are you crazy
the server gave him
a night off. You know drunk. I
don't like to drink but I'm not
drunk I suppose to be stupid to ask where
you are as it would sound I'm not leaving
it ask him when I get I just got my aunts
and there are no more questions. No
I know what I need to know. The Superman
Sam The dirty little boy from the other
side of the tracks I'll go and change I
wouldn't want him to see me in the same
dress twice.
Come in.
On Me. Living it but not Tony.
It's. Luck. I came
back you with you because you said you
didn't like to be pushed around I liked you
when you said that you were
looking for trouble but it was
a good kind of time and now Now
Sam I saw Are you going to get
her to leave or stay and leave this
town even without me but leave I
can't least not just yet.
You're going to need some
money. That's pretty clean.
See around yeah.
Martha stead getting
dressed for the occasion.
Why did they call me got
a riddle saddle if you can help it stop.
A little rattle called wants to be down
about me. And you. Sound just like
a fraud if it arrived it was
a rhyme with Mary. He's
drunk he's been sitting here
drinking all night. Draw
a chalk line and walking off like
a mental test any question like. What is
my object in life I tried to stop him from
Chloe euro Isaac and anger boy you know
all the answers don't you how are you
wondering and I was glad ecology I was
president of I'm Sam She was frightened of
me I had a dream Santa was about
you in my dream you were not
a hand there was some other and other
dreams There were told you he's drunk that
you say others many other he's lying to
him I said life was so. Is that what
you told You say I don't want to be in his
sand they can get out here all of them.
Every one of them rolled into one Tim Maybe
I'm talking I'm all of them rolled into
one. Gymnasium instructor in Philadelphia
with the muscle for a brain and
a tendency to in separate
verse you're a guy just
a guy named Pete an area who smells the
same thing. As greatest for backing your
from two bar exam but you want to
be an industrial engineer. You're
a guy you came along to fix
a tire so well you became
a city paid inspect and you're
a lot of us but worst of all you're the
one and only man who shares with me the
only claim I have. Askers Seder Mark
is always true so what if it is
what did you expect you never wanted to
marry you if you had any self respect you
married me because he felt
that way I would never tell
a lie old man Forster how long you
expect to go on paying off or whatever
happens to you you've got coming quite going
to heaven shall I tell you. He'll try
to get you to kill me like he got me to
send an innocent man to the Gap I told you
the way it was it was his father's idea he
need to tell you how she stood up in the
police station how she looked at the man
without batting an eye she said yes that's
the man he's the one who came into the
house that night he's the man who killed
Maya that even stuck in the
throat of my father. My poor
dear departed greedy for.
But you were right. And so
did I he's lying you believe me don't you
say Iris and. I have at least tell the
truth now tell how much you were
afraid of an unsolved murder now what
a threat it was to the power of the riches
that you're going to love so much that
I've learned to to love. How fire
became district attorney tell
a lie you may be hanged that can tell the
tricolor truth and likely just both of
them they wanted I don't want
a reason you are making
you happy I am not. Your
insane. You're out of
your mind. Snakes you.
Can see Sam how close we really are to each
other. Come pray go are happy I'm going
to have to be you or me. And unless
you do it now it will be you.
Much you think I'm drunk
I'm not. Just an say.
In China Japan. Saying.
Ask for help. Please.
Can you believe me don't you.
Understand do it now for the free and both
of these free without of course watch
a skull that's how we die
everybody knows what
a heavy drinker. Home fans can. Do
need. To know.
You.
Know I thought you loved me of that I did
too. Now you hate him. Now I'm sorry
for you. I dreamed that you
coming back to life this
dream I thought you'd be the same I knew
Is it true you're sick I could run to
when I was. In your mind that's where you're
sick and you'd help the sick that you
don't even know the difference between
right and wrong. Use killed testily new
record I've never murdered.
Your eyes. Still on the stairs.
I remember. You carried me in
here. Yeah.
To chant.
With my friend. That I didn't know
the difference between right.
What's right for water and ice to tell the
truth I think so yes and hang for you
wouldn't think for another to
confess your due time sure
a rot in prison for the rest of my life or
for what what am I guilty of murder what
were their lives compared to mine
what we see human beings Bishop
a fellow woman who never did anything to
anybody look what I've done with what
she's left I've given to charity built
schools hospitals getting thousands of
people work what was he I know it can be
my drug someone who would have died in the
gutter anyway either one of them had a
right to live if you didn't think for
a day to. Day I'm.
Going I'm going. To do it I
says Well because. I heard you
can't let him go can you.
Mind this waiting for your answer. Don't
be afraid of him we couldn't live that way
with the foo to let him go alone
time with your plan I have
a little trouble squaring this with you
broke into the house you demanded money you
tried to attack me and I
shot you in self-defense
a right to kill in self-defense that's
what the law says doesn't want to.
Isn't that what the. Moses books.
Hold up water. Man with
a police record. To. Usually
you have
a perfect case if you're the
award we're wishing. You want to
bed. Early.
Early.
To know. The A.T.M.
The old. Old age
a lump. You know that.
Didn't that's why you don't. I was afraid
for the first time in my life I was
afraid. I still could no longer
stand by. That you please.
I'm
a view. I've known you.
A tough time. It's not
your fault. It isn't
this it will. Come I am
a father so I hear it's not anyone's fault
it's just the way things and. People
walk I'd say it was.
Hard for them to get in.
Is near the gate. The plan is going.
Well we should be no he won't or that he
will. That he'll never tell you needn't be
afraid. In your seat. And really
different now between you and.
Just like. It's like nothing ever.
Changed like nothing ever. Will keep.
You through. It believe
me. You.
To.
Earl. You.
Either.
Nice to me.
You.
Can.
I missed the bus want to know I was
lucky. I wanted to see if I could be
a kid twice.
DON'T LOOK BACK BABY. Don't ever
look back. You know what happened
a Lot's wife. Who's wife. Sam to.
Change.